You don't want no coffee, man?
No. I generally like to cleanse
before I go all in.
That's a nice hat.
Thank you, man.
Yeah, I like the tone
of purple. It's nice.
- On my skin, right?
- Yeah.
Thank you.
You want to split it?
I just said that.
Oh. Well, thank you, man.
I really appreciate it.
Stand-up guy.
- Morning, fellas.
- Mm.
Uh, you guys still doing
that thing
I'm not supposed to know about
for insurance purposes?
Yes, we are.
This should help you out.
- Spa passes?
- Mm-hmm.
Nice. "90-minute massage,
a facial, sauna
and a cold plunge."
Senses gonna be lit.
Do I got to get naked
for this shit?
Nudity isn't...
required, I think.
Shi... I don't know, nigga.
Europe.
All right. It's time.
Let's do it.
You want me to pay for that?
Nigga, I already did that.
Right. All right.
You want...
- Nah, I'm good.
- You sure? All right.
Have fun, y'all.
A'ight.
See you later, alligator.
So, I know people
call them drugs,
but I like to think
of them as more
spiritual expanding apparatuses.
Nah, nigga. They drugs.
It's drugs.
Anyway, this one is called a
Nepalese Spacecake, all right?
The ingredients are harvested
from, uh, monks in Denmark.
The consensus is that it's weed
mixed with, uh,
Nepalese hallucinogenic honey,
but no one knows what's in them
for sure for sure.
Now, they're banned
in the U.S., right?
And you don't want to get them
off the black market,
'cause that's just a problem.
But I finally managed to
track down a place that's legit.
Got a ton of recs on Reddit.
Oh, yeah.
That's a tourist. Al?
- Huh?
- Don't be like him.
- Hey.
- What up?
I'll just do one cup
of hot coffee
and a Nepalese Spacecake.
- All right.
Keep the change.
Sorry, man.
That's not enough.
Oh.
Well, I'll just let fate
take care of it.
I'll pay for it, man.
Damn, just move.
Thank you, fate.
I'll have the same thing, man.
Okay.
Thanks, man.
Your friend, you know,
he kind of seems like he's seen
the other side before, but, uh,
are you sure you want this?
My nigga, I had to watch
the movie Cats sober
with a bitch who lied to me
about having some dank, okay?
So I know extremes. Yes.
All right, man.
Oh.
- There you go, man.
- Okay.
- Danke.
- Cats is underrated.
I'm just saying.
Talking to me like
I ain't never taken drugs.
Ah, yes. Here we are.
Yeah!
Nepalese.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Before you do that,
let the center be melted
by the heat of the coffee.
Yeah, that's-that's...
All right.
Hey, Al, whatever happens,
just know that
I love you very much.
Okay.
- Let's do this.
- Mm.
- All right, man. What now?
Music and a stroll to the spa.
Here. Take that.
- Oh.
- Nigga, iPod Nanos?
- Yes, sir.
I made us some playlists to help
- guide the honey through us.
- All right.
All right, now,
I'm gonna be listening
to  The Plane by Tomita.
Excuse me. And I got you
on some Stereolab shit.
Stereolab? All right, man.
Al, this is gonna be amazing.
I'm feeling it, man.
Let's do it.
Oh, shit!
Poor thing.
He's probably just sick. Hmm.
All right.
Come on. I think it's this way.
How long before
this shit kick in?
I'm pretty sure
I'm already high.
Nigga, no you are not.
'Cause I don't feel
a damn thing.
Man, this cookie is
definitely working,
and that is for certain.
See, your ass
is sober enough to rap.
No, man.
I'm too high to not rap.
Tell me what you think about...
Man, you have
any idea where we going?
Yeah. Actually, I think
there's a shortcut this way.
Come on.
Where are all the Black people
in Amsterdam?
We just passed two.
- There's a third one
right there.
- This way. This way. All right.
Hey, man. Hey, man,
I don't want to...
Come on, man. All them tourists.
I know, I know. It's only seven
more minutes this way.
Nigga, you gonna be my security?
Darius, man!
Actually, actually, no.
It's this way.
Oh, my God.
No, if this is guiding me right,
it should be...
Fuck off.
- Hold up, hold up, hold up.
- What?
- Is that... is that Paper Boi?
- No. Fuck off.
- Yes, man. That's him.
- Shit.
- No fucking way.
- Really? Which one?
The one with the fucking hat!
Hey, Paper Boi! Hey, Paper Boi!
- Paper Boi!
- Look at the hat!
- Don't-don't ignore me,
you bloody cunt!
I want an autograph!
- Paper Boi!
- I need your picture. I need it.
- Fancy a girl, Paper Boi?
- Hey, you fancy a wank?
- Hey, Paper Boi!
- Ooh, Paper Boi!
- Hey! Paper Boi!
- Paper Boi!
- Where are you at, Paper Boi?!
- He left!
Where the...
where the fuck is he?
- Come on, come on!
Help. Help.
Hey. You...
- You all right?
You-you in danger? You...
C-Can you tell me
what's-what's going on?
- You all right?
What?
- Well, blink twice if you...
- Shh.
If you can't tell me
what's going on...
- I'm just trying to...
- You ain't got to get
all ir...
Oh, God...
Oh.
- I'm sorry.
- Uh, I'm sorry
I interrupt... Okay.
Damn, your hat looks dumb.
Hmm?
I said your hat--
it's not working.
Well, I ain't ask your ass.
Wait. Hold on. Let me...
let me ask you something.
You need a friend?
I have friends. Thanks.
Yeah, but, like,
good ones, though.
Because a good friend
would've told you
that Chanel is for women.
Art is such a racket, no?
Then why bring your ass to
a museum if you don't like art?
To read people, my love.
Why else?
And look at the talent
right in front of us.
Wow. Prime example.
Tragically Arab. The style.
Like, ugh.
And then we have
our hypebeast faggots,
but, I mean, like,
that's an Alexander Wang story.
You should look it up.
It's really touchy, you know.
People get really sensitive...
And then, of course,
in front of us, we have
our statuesque white Lizzo.
I mean, honestly,
Lizzo's
kind of like white Lizzo,
- for real, for real,
because she's just so...
Why are you here?
Because I had to be. All right?
Oh, really?
School field trip?
Hiding out?
Are you someone
to other people?
I'm nobody,
so you can leave me alone.
Well,
everyone is nobody.
But are you a nobody
to everyone?
You're a rapper.
God, another one.
I hate rappers.
I most of all hate the way
y'all say "pussy."
Babe.
Look at me.
Soft.
Pussy.
I mean, I kind of hate
all rap music right now, though.
It's nothing personal.
I'm just...
- not a fan.
- Oh, that's good,
'cause I ain't a fan
of your ass, so we even.
Babe, I don't care.
I promise you,
I don't even give a fuck.
You know,
the thing about rappers, though,
is, like, y'all don't know
anything about yourselves.
Like... you have no idea
where your money is.
And I-I watch y'all's
interviews, you know?
You're wearing
all that designer.
And, I mean, you look cute.
It's no shade or whatever.
Do your thing.
But you still have no clue
where your money is
or where your money's going.
Well, that ain't me, a'ight?
Huh.
So...
who owns your masters?
What?
Who owns your masters?
The recording from which all
the later copies of your music
are made.
It's potentially
the most lucrative part
of making music, babe.
No one ever told you that?
That's funny!
Wow. I came at the perfect time.
I swear, I'm an angel.
Lorraine.
Al.
Hey, look,
how I get out of here?
You can start by taking off
that hat.
Yo, I'm being real.
If you are "famous,"
that shit
is making you stand out.
But wait here, though.
Don't go nowhere.
Here.
Fuck.
Stop.
Become what you fear.
Less attitude.
Put it on.
Take my help and let's go.
I know just where to hide out.
Oh, shit, it's night?
We only get
a little bit of sunlight.
Amsterdam-- city of dreams.
Ooh.
Hey.
Come on. Keep up.
Oh.
Hey.
Hey, Lorraine.
Come on.
Yeah, but where you at, girl?
Follow my voice.
Sorry. Excuse me.
Hey, L-Lorraine, though.
Lorraine.
Where...
Hey, Lorraine!
- Babe.
- Huh?
I need you to chill.
I'm right here. Come on.
All right.
Hold up, hold up, hold up.
Oh, you're gonna love
this place.
It's very exclusive.
- Lorraine, baby.
- Cammy!
- Finally.
- How are you?
Good.
Ooh, I love this.
You look like the future.
Oh, stop! Stop. Stop.
- You look amazing.
- You look so good.
- Hey.
- Mwah. Mwah.
And who's this?
Oh. This is my new friend.
- He like your old friend?
- Stop.
- This is Al.
- Hello.
Hey, y'all.
Hey.
Get behind me.
- Hey.
- Who's this?
- Paper Boi.
- Baby, this is New Jazz.
Ah, New Jazz.
Please, come in.
Hey.
Um, what's New Jazz?
Girl, I can't believe
you said that.
These white people
don't want us here anyway.
At least we can have some fun.
Yeah, but if you start saying
"New Jazz" for everyone
you bring in here, they're gonna
start asking questions.
Um, they should be
asking questions.
We're all New Jazz, baby.
Don't worry.
You high yet?
No.
Mm.
Come on.
Ladies, New Jazz,
what can I get you?
Two dirty martinis,
a gin and Hpnotiq,
and...
Uh, White Hennessy, neat.
Two dirties, a Blue Lagoon
and a Chris Evans.
Excellent. All of your drinks
have been covered
by that table over there.
Thank you.
So,
who are you, sir?
I'm a rapper.
Do you know Dua Lipa?
- Not really, no.
- Ugh!
She's my life. I love her.
Protect her, okay?
I'll try.
What's DaBaby like?
Ugh, I just want
to shave that little mustache
- and sit on his face.
Why the hat?
Oh, this, uh...
I just, um...
I picked it up at a museum
when I was ducking out
from these kids
that was chasing me.
- So I just...
- I love it.
It's very New Jazz.
How long have you and Lorraine
been fucking?
We're not fucking.
You're not the first rapper,
just so you know.
They all come out here.
Don't worry. She's discreet.
Well, I'm not worried 'cause...
I'm not worried
'cause we ain't...
we ain't fucking, so...
- Mm-hmm.
Do you know what they call
her apartment?
106 & Park.
- 106 & Park. 106...
You know, I'm-a get me a...
- ...a pre-drink drink.
You want something? No,
I'm-a get... I'm-a... I'm-a...
- I'm-a go.
- Oh.
'Cause-'cause...
the f-fuck.
- They definitely fucked.
- Mm.
Hey, man. Uh, White Hennessy,
neat, please.
Thank you.
Hey. I know you.
You're-you're that rapper,
right?
Paper Boi. Yeah.
- Yeah.
Um, ain't you, uh...
You...
- You, uh...
- Oh, yeah.
"I've got a particular set
of skills."
- Oh, shit.
Man, you about the last nigga...
person I expect to see in here,
man.
Yeah, oh,
I don't think anyone expects
- to see anyone in here, mate.
- Right?
Right, man. I mean...
I mean, this place is,
like, weird, right?
Like... like, it's weird.
I mean, I ain't... I ain't never
been no place like this before.
Well, it's... it's unreal,
all right.
Damn.
How'd you get here?
Uh... I just followed a local.
Mm. What'd they do?
What you mean?
Well, did they strangle a fan
or shag a teenager?
How'd they get in?
Uh... Thank you.
Ah, you don't have to say.
It's fine.
It's your business.
You might have heard
or read about my transgression.
You know, what I said about what
I wanted to do to a Black guy--
any Black guy-- when I was
a younger man in London.
A friend of mine had been raped,
and I acted out of anger.
I look back now,
and it honestly frightens me.
I thought people knowing
who I once was
would make clear who I am,
who I've become.
But, with all that being said...
I am sorry.
I apologize if I hurt people.
Yeah, well...
between you and me...
I still fuck with Taken.
Shit, man. Look,
it's good to know that you...
it's good to know that you
don't hate Black people now.
- You know?
- What? No, no, no, no.
I can't stand the lot of you.
Well, now I feel that way.
Because you tried
to ruin my career.
Didn't succeed, mind you.
However...
I'm sure one day
I will get over it.
But until then,
we are mortal enemies.
I'll see you around, big lad.
Yeah. All right, man.
Yeah, yeah.
Hold on, hold on, hold...
Wait.
But didn't you learn that you
shouldn't say shit like that?
Aye.
But I also learned
that the best and worst part
about being white is...
we don't have to learn anything
if we don't want to.
Take it easy, Paper Boi.
Hello, everyone.
We have a very special guest
planned for you.
At every one of these
engagements, we try to bring you
the finest and brightest
in culture,
the newest and most enticing
of the art form.
And tonight's no different.
- In the urban jungle,
- surrounded by
the harsh climate of men...
- Psst.
- ...the caged bird sings a song.
- Psst. Come on.
- What?
- Come on.
Hell no.
What you mean? Come on.
- Get your ass up. Get up.
Come on. Faster.
...never-before-seen
treasure of the modern...
The hell you been?
Aw, you be scared?
We clownin' on.
Oh, come on. Let's go.
Here, all the way from America,
just for you,
please welcome...
New Jazz!
Look, where the fuck we going?
Hey.
- It's cold as fuck.
Wait, the sun is out? Shit.
Oh, my gosh.
I am in so much trouble.
They gonna be so mad at me.
But ha!
Yo,
they was gonna make you perform
back there.
Well, I know how to say no.
Yeah, they don't... they don't
let you say no in there.
Know what? Don't worry.
I got you.
Hey, what's wrong with you?
Uh-uh. What's wrong with you?
Look, just don't-don't touch
my face, all right?
Uh, nigga,
I just saved your life.
Ha, the fuck you did.
Wow!
Well, it's very clear
you don't trust me.
Yeah,
'cause you shit on me all day!
All day! That's all you do.
Call me stupid. Why the fuck
would I trust your ass?
Oh, pussy boy got balls
but can't take the truth?
- The fuck you say?
- Nigga, all day,
I've been telling you
what you needed to hear,
not what the fuck
you wanted to hear!
- Fuck out of here, man.
- No.
If you don't have that,
guess what--
you're fucking white!
Nigga.
Your friends.
Your friends let you wear
that shit hat.
They don't pay for shit.
You got family handling
the most important parts
of your fucking finances?
My nigga, your future?
All of 'em, all of 'em
got a vested interest
in you not seeing the truth.
You don't trust me?
I'm all you got.
Real quick, though--
who the fuck are you? Hmm?
The fuck you know about me?
You don't know shit.
My nigga, you don't feel shit.
Can't even feel your legs.
What you talking 'bout?
- You can't move.
Your legs don't work.
- Your arms,
- they don't work.
- The fu...
- Yeah.
I think
that you should sit down.
- Mm-hmm.
- Wow. Shh.
Shh. Yeah, I know.
- It's okay.
Shh. Shh.
But I finally managed to
track down a place that's legit.
- Got a ton of recs on Reddit.
Al. Don't be like him.
- Don't be like him.
Don't be like him.
Shit.
Hey.
I got you some room-temp water
on your nightstand.
And there's some, uh, food, too,
if you want me to heat it up.
What happened, man?
You passed out.
I found you on the street.
You've been asleep for, like...
ten hours.
Nigga,
did you change my clothes?
Yeah.
- It was not easy.
You vomited.
Oh, man.
Where's Lorraine?
Your mom?
Never mind.
I'm glad y'all didn't tell me
what y'all were up to.
This actually worked out better.
Text me if you need anything.
All right?
Earn.
Huh?
Who owns my masters?
When you were negotiating
my label contract...
...who owns my masters?
You do.
Thanks.
No problem.
I'll come back up and check
on you in, like, an hour.